

### ABOUT ME

I'm Fidalgo, a 23 years old self-taught Front-end developer, from Portugal. In October 2018 I decided it was time for a change, so I started to wake up at 6am to study javascript before going into work. I quickly started to love Javascript, and in January 2019 I decided to take the risk and quit my job. I've been studying Front-end development full time ever since. I always want to learn more, do more, and be more. I'm also a firm believer that we should never settle.

I'm hard working, super curious, passionate, committed, and also a fast learner!

hello@fidalgo.dev



www.fidalgodev.com



in in/fidalgodev



fidalgodev



(i) fidalgodev

# SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 - CSS3 - JAVASCRIPT - SASS - WEBPACK REDUX - STYLED COMPONENTS - CSS MODULES FIREBASE - BABEL - GRAPHQL - GATSBY - REACTJS

### **EDUCATION**

#### 04/2014 - 06/2017

### **COMMUNICATION AND MULTIMEDIA**

Universidade de Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro Vila Real, Portugal

EQF Level 4:

Web development (HTML, CSS and PHP);

Web Design;

Communication Skills;

History of Art.

### 09/2010 - 06/2013

### **TECHNICAL COURSE OF MULTIMEDIA**

Escola EB 2/3 c/ Secundário PAMF Murtosa, Portugal

EOF - Level 3 Video Editing; Design;

## CERTIFICATIONS

#### **UDEMY**

3D.

Advanced CSS and Sass The complete JavaScript course 2019 JavaScript: Understanding the Weird parts Modern React w/ Redux React - The complete guide

### **WESBOS**

JavaScript 30/ES6 for Everyone

## EXPERIENCE

### 09/2017 - 01/2019

### **WEB DEVELOPER**

**Invisual Branding Solutions** Aveiro, Portugal

Wordpress projects; Small management apps with PHP: Static websites using HTML5 and CSS3; Mobile Apps using PhoneGap.

### 10/2015 - 06/2017

#### LEADER OF WEB DEPARTMENT

Núcleo Estudantes Comunicação e Multimédia Vila Real, Portugal

Wordpress projects; Small management apps with PHP; Static websites using HTML5 and CSS3; Mobile Apps using PhoneGap.

### 10/2012 - 10/2013

### **FREELANCER**

Olhoshot

Ovar, Portugal

Developed several websites using HTML, CSS and Wordpress on the freelancing regime.

# 10/2012 - 10/2013

### INTERNSHIP

Olhoshot

Ovar, Portugal

Development of several websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and Wordpress.